<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Covid on The Manual</title><link>https://jessejaggars.com/tags/covid/</link><description>Recent content in Covid on The Manual</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 08:18:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jessejaggars.com/tags/covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Try Again</title><link>https://jessejaggars.com/post/try-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 08:18:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jessejaggars.com/post/try-again/</guid><description>In a few minutes I&amp;rsquo;ll be traveling back to Dunn to get my second dose of the Pfizer Covid-19 Vaccine. Last time (three weeks ago), the traffic was amazing. Possiblly the worst I had ever seen.
This time my wife is going too and we have a plan to let me disembark near the site and she will find a place to park that is easy to get to.
It feels like one of those plans that sounds very clever in advance but might go poorly because everyone else has the same idea.</description></item><item><title>Denied</title><link>https://jessejaggars.com/post/denied/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 12:50:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jessejaggars.com/post/denied/</guid><description>I thought I was going to receive my second Pfizer vaccine today. I showed up on time with my documentation, and handed it over to the lady behind the sign-up desk.
She took a quick look at my card, and asked me if I had already had my first shot. It seemed odd to me that she would ask, because I just presented my card as evidence that I had.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer dose #2 incoming</title><link>https://jessejaggars.com/post/pfz2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 11:38:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jessejaggars.com/post/pfz2/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll receive my second dose of the Pfizer Sars-Cov-2 vaccine on Wednesday and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty mixed about it.
On one hand, I feel great that I&amp;rsquo;m on my way to be about as protected as I can be against the disease as well as reducing my chances at spreading it to others.
On the other, my son cannot be vaccinated (he&amp;rsquo;s three), and so many other people have suffered over the past year, that it&amp;rsquo;s just plain hard to be elated.</description></item></channel></rss>